[Music]
i pull players
hope you enjoyed those two little kick
shots and i have a nice secret i want to
share with you
about the last one you know what's
important
and what's the key to make this cuba
stick
and slide behind these two balls here
that
is to use a lot of top spin
if you don't the cue ball will get away
from these balls and it will never stop
there
because what a lot of maybe amateur
players don't realize
the top spin that's on the ball it keeps
spinning
and turning and turning and when it hits
this rail
it's it actually reverses and now the
topspin
becomes a stop shot or actually
sometimes even a draw shot
so if you put enough top spin and speed
also in this three on this ball
it will actually
do that send that one away
and the cue ball will stay there nice
and crisp
but there's another tip that i want to
share with you and that's a mental tip
because it's actually a trap and that is
if you can do these shots in practice
there can be an expectation that you
should be able to do it all the time
and you know what happens with an
expectation when you expect something
you become
passive you stop working for it
and you start waiting for the result to
happen instead of working
for it and that is a mental trap
especially in matches this can be a very
tricky thing we have to stay
humble towards the game respect it
and don't expect everything to happen
automatically
another big thing in mental match play
guys
is tilt mistake tilt
bad luck tilt opponent tilt equipment
tilt you name it
all very challenging topics because
how do you cope with making a big
blunder
and then coming back and making a great
shot
to save the match i have a great example
for you guys
from a world cup of pool match from a
few years back
i make a big blunder and then i recover
with a great
shot afterwards to save the game check
it out here's the safety blunder on the
2 ball
i under hit that stroke wasn't sure if i
wanted to roll it behind the six
off the rail or stop it i came with a
poor stroke
and that caused us the rack and now it
went eight
eight instead of nine seven so i was
suffering there from a steak tilt
but i caught myself and i said my next
inning at the table will be my
best inning this was on eight eight
my next inning and that mental state of
mind
won us the game we got ball in hand
there and nick made a beautiful 2-9
combo
to put us in the semi-finals
and that's exactly the reason why i've
made this new course
mental match play for competitive pool
players
to deal with the mental traps
and all the tilt and you can stay in
balance and correct yourself
in the match itself so you could make a
mistake
but you can correct and come back and
actually play a great shot in your next
inning that's
all about mental power strength
and a comeback state of mind which you
can train
so let's have a look at the curriculum
and what you can take away from this
course
so here you can see the overview of the
and as you can see there's the
expectations
versus goals that's the solution
comparing yourself to others
very dangerous a whole bunch of tilt
plus the solution guys then also
two very strong topics shaming
projection
and open wounds stuff that players don't
like to talk about but that they carry
on their backs
for years bad losses shame
embarrassment we have to try to get that
to the surface deal with it so we become
more free and get our joy back in the
game
and start winning more games when you're
done with this course you can
confidently handle
various forms of tilt and maintain a
solid composure in your matches
and you're gonna have multiple tools to
hold on in those
tough match situations and climb back
into good form
so if you want to become a better player
and start winning more matches
come and join me in this course click
the link below
and i'm gonna see you right there take
care